<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Smart Docs</title>
      <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Smart Docs</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Community Lean Coffee</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Community-Lean-Coffee</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Community-Lean-Coffee</guid>
    <description>Our Lean Coffee meetings are an open, collaborative space where members of the Smart Connections community come together to share ideas, discuss topics of interest, and build connections ...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 23:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Smart Ecosystem Documentation</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Smart Ecosystem Documentation Empowering Individuals with AI through Open-Source Tools The Smart Ecosystem is a suite of open-source tools designed to integrate ...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:44:10 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Smart Connect Update: Let&#039;s Dive into Community Actions and Custom GPTs</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connect-app/Videos/Smart-Connect-Update-2024-10-31</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connect-app/Videos/Smart-Connect-Update-2024-10-31</guid>
    <description> Hey there, it’s Brian. Today, I want to walk you through a feature update I just shipped in Smart Connect, something I’m pretty excited to share—Community Actions.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:44:10 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Overview</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connect-app/SC-App-docs</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connect-app/SC-App-docs</guid>
    <description>A standalone application that connects ChatGPT to the Smart Environment on your local computer. Key Features Editing Capabilities: Allows ChatGPT to read and edit your local notes.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 21:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Community Lean Coffee 2024-10-31</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Community-Lean-Coffee/Community-Lean-Coffee-2024-10-31</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Community-Lean-Coffee/Community-Lean-Coffee-2024-10-31</guid>
    <description> 🌴 Brian’s notes Search in Smart Chat and Roadmap I’ve been working on enhancing the Smart Chat functionality within Obsidian. Currently, the existing version of Smart Chat is limited to single-step interactions, and it’s somewhat outdated.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:44:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Smart Environments in Smart Connect</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connect-app/Smart-Environments-in-Smart-Connect</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connect-app/Smart-Environments-in-Smart-Connect</guid>
    <description>Smart Environments are a core component of the Smart Connect app, designed to provide seamless integration between your local notes and AI-powered processing ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:15:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Connections pane</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connections-Obsidian-plugin/Connections-pane-(Smart-Connections-view)</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connections-Obsidian-plugin/Connections-pane-(Smart-Connections-view)</guid>
    <description> why Linking relevant notes is a best practice in most personal knowledge management (PKM) systems. Unfortunately, this is a time consuming process and linking to all relevant content has many undesired side effects.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:15:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Commands</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connections-Obsidian-plugin/SC-Commands-docs</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connections-Obsidian-plugin/SC-Commands-docs</guid>
    <description>Commands in the Obsidian Smart Connections plugin are accessed using the Obsidian Command palette. Random Note opens a random note from the connections to the current note Refresh &amp; Make Connections recreates the embedding for the current note and refreshes the Connections pane (Smart Connections view) Open: Connections pane (Smart Connections view; “Find Connections”) Smart Lookup (semantic search) pane ChatGPT pane Smart Chat .</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:15:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>FAQs</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connections-Obsidian-plugin/Smart-Connections-FAQs</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Smart-Connections-Obsidian-plugin/Smart-Connections-FAQs</guid>
    <description>+Documenting SC SC is designed for “reasonable” individual usage. While it should work, an increase in issues should be expected with large datasets (&gt;10k notes) Can I use Smart Connections without Smart Connect? Yes, Smart Connections can be used independently within Obsidian.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:15:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Stability vs Innovation in the Smart Ecosystem</title>
    <link>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Blog/Stability-vs-Innovation-in-the-Smart-Ecosystem</link>
    <guid>https://docs.smartconnections.app/Blog/Stability-vs-Innovation-in-the-Smart-Ecosystem</guid>
    <description>I wanted to take a moment to address a topic that’s been on my mind lately: the balance between stability and innovation within our Smart Ecosystem. As many of you know, our primary mission is to empower individuals with AI through open-source software.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 20:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>